let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the <b> Velency </b> of Boron",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the of <b> Atomicity </b> Hydrogen?",
    answer: "Diatomic",
    options: [
      "Monoatomic",
      "Diatomic",
      "Triatomic",
      "Polyatomic"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a <b> Physical Change </b>?",
    answer: "Brwoning of Fruits",
    options: [
      "Melting of Ice",
      "Shredding Paper",
      "Chopping of Wood",
      "Brwoning of Fruits"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following can be done to prevent <b>Rusting </b>?",
    answer: "All of the Above",
    options: [
      "Enamelling",
      "Tinning",
      "Electroplating",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The process of depositing a coating of zinc metal on iron objects is known as ______________.",
    answer: "Galvanisation",
    options: [
      "Galvanisation",
      "Tinning",
      "Enamelling",
      "Painting"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is the chemical formulae of <b> Sodium Hydroxide </b> ?",
    answer: "NaOh",
    options: [
      "NaCl",
      "NaOh",
      "NaHCO3",
      "MgO"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not an <b> Element </b> ?",
    answer: "Water",
    options: [
      "Oxygen",
      "Gold",
      "Silver",
      "Water"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following substances is not important for <b> Rusting </b>?",
    answer: "Carbon Dioxide",
    options: [
      "Carbon Dioxide",
      "Oxygen",
      "Moisture",
      "Both b and c"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following acids is found in <b> Vinegar </b>?",
    answer: "Acetic Acid",
    options: [
      "Citric Acid",
      "Lactic Acid",
      "Acetic Acid",
      "Tartaric Acid"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following acids is found in <b> Ant Sting </b>? ",
    answer: "Formic Acid",
    options: [
      "Oxalic Acid",
      "Formic Acid",
      "Malic Acid",
      "Nitric Acid"
    ]
  },



];